[
    {
        "front": "Jikan",
        "back": "Time",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Gozen",
        "back": "A.M.",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Gogo",
        "back": "P.M.",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Ima ",
        "back": "Now",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Shucchō",
        "back": "Business Trip",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Kara",
        "back": "From",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Made",
        "back": "Till",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Itsu",
        "back": "When",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Tanjōbi",
        "back": "Birthday",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Sei nen gappi",
        "back": "D.O.B.",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Nanji",
        "back": "What Time",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Nanyōbi",
        "back": "What Day",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Nan nichi",
        "back": "What Date",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Ototoi",
        "back": "Day before yesterday ",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Kinō",
        "back": "Yesterday",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Kyō",
        "back": "Today",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Ashita",
        "back": "Tomorrow",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Asatte",
        "back": "Day after tomorrow",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Ryokō",
        "back": "Travel, Trip",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Deshita",
        "back": "Past form of des",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Oshōgatsu",
        "back": "New Year",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Shiken",
        "back": "Exam",
        "chapter": 3
    },
    {
        "front": "Kaimono",
        "back": "Shopping",
        "chapter": 3
    }
]